
Technique: [Axial proton density and fat suppressed proton density. Coronal T1 and STIR. Sagittal STIR.]

Comparison: [no previous relevant imaging is available for comparison.]

Findings:

Bones and soft tissues: [No fluid collection. No bone marrow oedema. No focal bone lesion. (screen fat suppressed images)]

Joints: [No significant joint effusion. No capsular thickening.]

Ligaments: [Normal ankle joint alignment. Normal medial and lateral ligamentous complexes. Normal plantar fascia origin.]

Tendons: [Normal appearances of the medial and peroneal flexor tendons. Normal extensor tendons. Normal Achilles' tendon. (four quadrant approach)]


Impression: []

