
CONSENT:
WHO form completed.
Informed written consent. Risk of infection, nerve root injury, bleeding/haematoma, inadequate response.

PREPARATION:
Aseptic technique.
4 mL 1% lidocaine to the skin and subcutaneous soft tissues

PROCEDURE:
Needle inserted down to the LEFT S1 nerve root. Position confirmed with CT.
40 mg of Depo-Medrone steroid and 1.5 mL of 0.25% levobupivacaine was injected around the LEFT S1 nerve root.
No immediate complications.


FOLLOW UP:
Pain diary provided.
